<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>My New Hugo Site</title>
    <link>http://example.org/</link>
    <description>Recent content on My New Hugo Site</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 30 Jan 2021 21:19:39 +0100</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="http://example.org/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Experiences</title>
      <link>http://example.org/experiences/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 30 Jan 2021 21:19:39 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.org/experiences/</guid>
      <description>Experience Below an overview about my past experiences professional and in teaching. For more details refer to my cv.
PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE Raicoon  Vienna, Austria Data Scientist, Software Developer, Since June 2020
  Using statistical analysis to detect recurrent device faults in solar plants Building and maintaining an automatic fault reporting and ticketing engine for solar plant operators Constructing a validation and labeling infrastructure for data analysis  University of Notre Dame  Notre Dame, IN Graduate Research Assistant, Computer Science and Engineering July 2016 – May 2020</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Overview</title>
      <link>http://example.org/overview/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 30 Jan 2021 21:19:39 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.org/overview/</guid>
      <description>Martin Imre, PhD ![[me.png]] Welcome to my website. let me introduce myself I&amp;rsquo;m a Data Scientist/Software Developer working on automizing fault detection for solar plants. My scientific interests lie in machine &amp;amp; deep learning, high performance computing, and interactive data analysis &amp;amp; visualization.
Feel free to explore the other pages to find out more about me, my experiences, and publications.
email</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Publications</title>
      <link>http://example.org/publications/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 30 Jan 2021 21:19:39 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.org/publications/</guid>
      <description>Publications and Presentations  PUBLICATIONS  2020 Imre, Martin, Wenqing Chang, Shuzhan Wang, Christine Trinter and Chaoli Wang &amp;ldquo;GraphVisual: Design and Evaluation of a Web-Based Visualization Tool for Teaching and Learning Graph Visualization” Proceedings of American Society for Engineering Education Annual Conference, Montreal, Canada, Jun 2020 PDF Source Demo Cite
Imre, Martin, Jun Tao, Yongyu Wang, Zhiqiang Zhao, Zhuo Feng, and Chaoli Wang. &amp;ldquo;Spectrum-preserving sparsification for visualization of big graphs.&amp;quot; Computers &amp;amp; Graphics 87 (2020): 89-102.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Short Bio</title>
      <link>http://example.org/short-bio/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 30 Jan 2021 21:19:39 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.org/short-bio/</guid>
      <description>I&amp;rsquo;m a Data Scientist/Software Developer working on automizing fault detection for solar plants. My scientific interests lie in machine &amp;amp; deep learning, high performance computing, and interactive data analysis &amp;amp; visualization.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Bio</title>
      <link>http://example.org/bio/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 30 Jan 2021 21:19:38 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.org/bio/</guid>
      <description>Martin Imre is currently working as Data Scientist/Software Developer at greentec development gmbh developing parts of an automatic fault detection engine for solar plants. He received his PhD in Computer Science from the University of Notre Dame in May 2020 researching high-performance data analysis methods for scientific data visualization. Before his PhD studies he received an MSc and BSc in Software Engineering in 2016 and 2014 respectively.
Besides teaching and research experience, he has collected professional experience during internships at the MCS Department at Argonne National Lab (Lemont, IL May - July 2018), the Secure Systems and Software Lab at University of California Irvine (July - Sept.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Concept</title>
      <link>http://example.org/concept/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 30 Jan 2021 21:19:38 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.org/concept/</guid>
      <description>Concept [[Overview]]  Write [[Short Bio]] Write &amp;ldquo;news&amp;rdquo; Add email Add links  Add link github Add link to linkedin Add link to CV Google Scholar Add images for the links  github linkedin cv google scholar     Add photo  [[Publications]]  List of publications Add links to open source repos Think about the link texts Add link to papers Download and host papers yourself LaTeX citation link  [[Experiences]]  Bascially CV stuff Summarize/sparsend out Add greentec/raicoon  [[Bio]]  Write the long bio [[Bio]]  [[Personal]]  stuff like bread Sport Beer?</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>